{
    "id": "c084ab2464384e64955613b7a7dadee5",
    "title": "Get and go exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5d9386fdbfe74b1580092a3854a70d6c",
            "title": "Get And Go",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I …………………… .. to work by car and Susie …………………… by train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go, go",
                        "go, goes",
                        "goes, goes"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s see who will ………………… there first?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………… to see him yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "went",
                        "got",
                        "gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although the train was late, I managed to …………………. to the meeting in time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "get"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It wasn’t easy to ………………… through the crowd.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "got"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could you tell me how to ……………………… to the post office?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We had better ………………… going – it’s late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is …………………… late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "going",
                        "getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When do I ………………… to see your new baby?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I couldn’t ………………….. the car to start.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}